[
    {
        "lessonId": "directions",
        "title": "Directions",
        "exercises": [
    {
      "front": "North",
      "back_hint": "Al-Shamāl",
      "back": "الشَمَالُ"
    },
    {
      "front": "East",
      "back_hint": "Al-Sharq",
      "back": "الشَّرْقُ"
    },
    {
      "front": "South",
      "back_hint": "Al-Janūb",
      "back": "الْجَنُوبُ"
    },
    {
      "front": "West",
      "back_hint": "Al-Gharb",
      "back": "الْغَرْبُ"
    },
    {
      "front": "Up",
      "back_hint": "Fawq",
      "back": "فَوْقَ"
    },
    {
      "front": "Under",
      "back_hint": "Taht",
      "back": "تَحْتَ"
    },
    {
      "front": "Next to",
      "back_hint": "Bijanibi",
      "back": "بِجَانِبِ"
    },
    {
      "front": "Inside",
      "back_hint": "Fi ad-dākhil",
      "back": "فِي الدَّاخِلِ"
    },
    {
      "front": "Outside",
      "back_hint": "Kharij",
      "back": "خَارِجٌ"
    },
    {
      "front": "On",
      "back_hint": "'Ala",
      "back": "عَلَى"
    },
    {
      "front": "In front",
      "back_hint": "Amāma",
      "back": "أَمَامَ"
    },
    {
      "front": "Behind",
      "back_hint": "Wara'",
      "back": "وَرَاءَ"
    },
    {
      "front": "Between",
      "back_hint": "Bayn",
      "back": "بَيْنَ"
    },
    {
      "front": "Left",
      "back_hint": "Yasar",
      "back": "يَسَارٌ"
    },
    {
      "front": "Right",
      "back_hint": "Yameen",
      "back": "يَمِينٌ"
    }
  ] 
    }
]